Do you think your bed is a safe haven of rest and peace?
你是否认为你的床是一个休息和宁静的安全港湾呢？
Do the tensions and stresses of the hard day's work drain away as you sink into the mattress and lay your weary head on a soft pillow?
当你陷入床垫中，把疲惫的头靠在柔软的枕头上的时候，是否感觉辛苦工作一天后的紧张和压力都消散了呢？
Well, you might not feel so relaxed if you knew that microscopic pests were lurking there!
嗯，如果你知道有微小的害虫正潜伏在那里，你可能就不会觉得那么放松了！
It seems that beds may not be such a good place for our health — actually they could be making us ill!
似乎床对于我们的健康来说可能并不是一个那么好的地方——实际上它们可能会让我们生病！
Recent studies have shown that bacteria, fungi and dust mites, some smaller than the diameter of a hair, live in our bedding.
最近的研究表明，细菌、真菌和尘螨（有些比头发的直径还小）生活在我们的床上用品中。
When we move around in our sleep, we disturb them and they are propelled into the air - which we then breathe in as we sleep.
当我们在睡梦中翻身时，我们会惊扰到它们，它们就会被抛到空气中——然后我们在睡觉时就会把它们吸入体内。
According to the American Lung Association, four out of five households in the United States now have high levels of dust mites, although it's not the mites themselves that cause the problems, but their droppings.
根据美国肺脏协会的说法，现在美国五分之四的家庭中都有大量的尘螨，不过引发问题的并不是螨虫本身，而是它们的排泄物。
These are "highly allergenic" according to Dr William Berger, a fellow with the American Academy of Allergy, Asthma and Immunology.
美国过敏、哮喘与免疫学学会的研究员威廉·伯杰博士称，这些排泄物“极易引发过敏”。
"Even if you aren't allergic... they can still irritate you, the way pepper would if it blew into your nose and eyes."
“即使你没有过敏体质......它们仍然会刺激你，就像胡椒粉吹进你的鼻子和眼睛里时的那种感觉。”
Brendan Boor, Assistant Professor of Civil Engineering, who carries out bed research, also found that bed dust in the air triggers allergies - causing watery eyes, sneezing, coughs and asthma.
土木工程助理教授布伦丹·布尔进行了有关床的研究，他还发现空气中的床上灰尘会引发过敏反应——导致眼睛流泪、打喷嚏、咳嗽和哮喘。
He has recommended ways to limit our exposure to these unsavoury allergens.
他推荐了一些方法来减少我们接触这些讨厌的过敏原。
Firstly, he suggests vacuuming your mattress regularly - weekly, or even daily.
首先，他建议定期——每周，甚至每天——用吸尘器清洁你的床垫。
He also recommends doing away with carpets and washing floors.
他还建议去除地毯并清洗地板。
Using allergen-proof bed covers, he says, can reduce the risk of getting allergies.
他说，使用防过敏的床罩可以降低过敏的风险。
In addition, washing bedding and pillows frequently can help, as can a portable air cleaner placed near the bed.
此外，经常清洗床上用品和枕头也会有所帮助，在床边放置一台便携式空气净化器也能起到作用。
If you do as Brendan Boor suggests, you will breathe in cleaner air as you sleep... or will you?
如果你按照布伦丹·布尔的建议去做，你在睡觉时就会吸入更清洁的空气......你会这样做吗？
Is it really safe for you to go back in your bed...?
对你来说，再回到床上真的安全吗......？